fiatforum.com 2019-05-14

# The FIAT Forum - Privacy Statement

The FIAT Forum has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of our shop, online services, websites, and web services ("Services"). 

This privacy policy governs the manner in which The FIAT Forum uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of our Services. 

**1\. Privacy**

The FIAT Forum is committed to developing long lasting relationships based on trust. As such, The FIAT Forum will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. Our Services are not directed at children under 13 years of age. 

**2\. Information We Collect**

The FIAT Forum may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. 

The information we collect is personal information that identifies you personally, such as: 

  * First & Last name 
  * Postal address 
  * Telephone and Fax numbers 
  * URL 
  * E-mail address 

The FIAT Forum may also collect information about how users access our Services using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies or other similar means. 

**3\. What are Cookies?**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive for an extended period of time. 

Your browser's help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by The FIAT Forum to track user preferences while the user is using our Services. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by The FIAT Forum to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on The FIAT Forum websites do not contain personally identifiable information. 

**3a. Google Cookies**

Google's use of the Double DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**4\. Log Files**

Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information. 

**5\. How we use this Information**

The FIAT Forum may use the personally identifiable information collected by The FIAT Forum to contact customers regarding products and services offered by The FIAT Forum and, to the extent the User has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 

We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our Services and marketing and sales efforts. The FIAT Forum will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorize such disclosures. 

**6\. Disclosure of Information**

The FIAT Forum may also disclose aggregate, anonymous, data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, statistical information only will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case The FIAT Forum is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners. 

**7\. Special Offers and Updates**

Our customers and users may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and possibly a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

**8\. Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**9\. Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on The FIAT Forum. 

The FIAT Forum websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that The FIAT Forum is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. The The FIAT Forum Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by The FIAT Forum. 

**10\. Maintenance of Information**

The information provided to The FIAT Forum is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by The FIAT Forum. The FIAT Forum employs industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. 

While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur; we make every effort to prevent such occurrences. 

**11\. Your Responsibility**

You are responsible for the security of the login information, such as usernames and passwords, which give you access to your private information maintained by The FIAT Forum. Make sure you keep login information in a safe place and do not share it with others. 

Note that key-loggers, viruses, or other surveillance devices can intercept login information on the computers from which you access our Services, so you should take precautions regarding such devices, especially from public computers. In addition, you should always log out from any relevant Services when you are not actively using them. 

**12\. Questions**

Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be directed to privacy@fiatforum.com.
